shoppingexpress.com.au 2014-04-18

# Online Privacy Policy – Secure Online Shopping| Shopping Express

In this privacy policy, the word "we", "our", "us", "ShoppingExpress" will be referring to Shopping Express Pty Ltd (ABN:65 146 078 319 ) and the word "you" and "your" will be referring to you the customer.

ShoppingExpress is an online department store that treats the privacy and sensitive data of our customers very seriously.  We are totally committed to protecting your privacy so as to provide a safe and secure shopping experience for you.  In the following paragraphs, we will be describing how the information you provided will be managed and kept secure by us.  We will also state what type of personal information we will be storing and what will not.  If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us on: [mail](mailto:mail@shoppingexpress.com.au)[@shoppingexpress.com.au](mailto:cs@shoppingexpress.com.au).

**Personal Information Collected From You**

ShoppingExpress collects personal information from you that are necessary for us to complete a transaction with you or to provide you with the information or service you requested.  This personal information collected may include: full name, email address, contact numbers, billing and shipping address.  Among the information collected, may be personal information of others not our customers but are provided by individuals or our customers in the process of completing the transaction.  This information may include: full name, email address, contact number, address, as well as other information about you that was provided during the process of completing the transaction.

At ShoppingExpress, the collected personal information’s sole purpose is to conduct our business and complete the transaction with you. Another purpose of your personal information, provided by you when you submitted us an email query, is to help us in communicating with you.  We will use the collected information such as your name and email address and other information you provide, to help facilitate in solving any issues you requested.  An example is using your information to follow up a tracking or dispatch process.

We may also use your personal information recorded, such as your email address as part of our email communications and marketing campaign, which you can unsubscribe easily if you choose to.  An example is our newsletter offering the latest products and news of our special promotions.  Each of our newsletters will consist of a link to unsubscribe and once you do that (always in a visible and easy to locate place), you will not receive our newsletter again, unless you chose to subscribe it again.  We may also use the personal information you provided for our marketing and website customisation.  An example of the type of information used, will be the suggestion you provided to us that help in our marketing campaign or website improvement.

**Personal Information Not Recorded**

Your personal information’s privacy is treated with special care and as such sensitive payment information such as credit card details will never be stored in our system.  The credit card information you key in during our secure checkout system will only be directed to our payment gateway SecurePay and these information will facilitate them in payment verification and approval.  We used Comodo, one of the most established Certification Authorities worldwide for our security certificate.  This security certificate encrypts and help to protect data during your checkout and payment process and any attempt to intercept this data will result in receiving random numbers and alphabetic characters instead. You will notice that you are entering a secure and encrypted page when you use our checkout system with the bottom of the page displaying a “small padlock” logo, and the web page address starting with https://.

**Security Measures To Protect Your Privacy**

We employ the best practices to protect the personal information provided by you; best practices including security measures and procedure considering the physical location, the electronic location, and the limitation of access and modification to your personal information.  We store your personal data in a secured physical location with limited access to users that need to access it only.  We employ firewalls, VPNs, anti-virus software and email filters to protect your personal data electronically.  We limit the access levels of users within [ShoppingExpress.com.au](http://shoppingexpress.com.au/) to the extent that the information provided by you is accessible only by the relevant person with the right to access. We also constantly review our procedures to consider in area of improvement to ensure your personal information kept with us is always secure.

**Personal Information Disclosure**

We will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone.  Your information will be disclosed outside of ShoppingExpress under the following conditions:

  1. You have given us your written consent to disclose this information to a third party

  2. It is required by Law or regulation requested by a government agency

  3. We suspect a customer may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices in which a government agency should be made aware of

  4. If your communications may potentially cause harm to others, the appropriate person will be notified.

**Links to Other Sites**

ShoppingExpress contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Therefore, please be aware that we are not responsible or bound by the privacy practices of these sites.  We strongly advise that you read the privacy policy of the other website that you visit when you leave our website.

**Changes and modification of Personal Information**

If you wish to change your personal information with us, or if you no longer wish to use our service, you may request that your web site account be deactivated by emailing us at: [mail](mailto:mail@shoppingexpress.com.au)[@shoppingexpress.com.au](mailto:mail@shoppingexpress.com.au)

**Cookies and Third Party Tracking**

When you visit ShoppingExpress, your PC will store a piece of information called “cookies” about our website into your hard drive.  Cookies cannot be use to run programs and their sole purpose is to improve your shopping experience to a website you visited before, by making your website load faster and more efficiently without having to retrieve some information that recorded by the cookies. The information recorded in cookie is only accessible by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie.

If you chose not to accept cookies from ShoppingExpress, you need to configure your browser to reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is sent.  Most web browsers accept cookies by default.

ShoppingExpress uses third party tracking services for market analysis and survey.  This third party tracking service will use web beacons (a string of code placed in the web page) to track and collect non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our website.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We will review our privacy policy from time to time.  If there is a need to change our policy, we reserve the right to do so.  Any changes will be updated and posted on our news page.

**Breach of Privacy**

If you have issues in regards to our privacy policy and would like to issue a complain or concern, we welcome you to contact us at: [mail](mailto:mail@shoppingexpress.com.au)[@shoppingexpress.com.au](mailto:mail@shoppingexpress.com.au).
